我就杀了她
I'll kill her.
该我了
My turn.
站住  克莱尔·黑尔  站住
Stop. Claire Hale. Stop!
"我想炸了她的眼球
"I'd like to fry her eyeballs.
如果没有别人敢杀了总统  我就去
If no one else steps up to kill the president, I will.
还当做一份美差"
I'd enjoy it."
这是一条北达科他州的推文
A tweet out of North Dakota.
还有吗
What else?
"上帝从未想要一个女人统治这片土地
"God never intended a woman to rule this land.
她是反基督
She is the anti-Christ.
-还是犹太人"  -犹太人
- And a Jew." - A Jew?
-我们真有必要听这些吗  -是的
- Do we really need to hear all of this? - Yes.
一篇未发表的社论
An unpublished editorial.
有个人拿枪指着你的肖像
Someone pointing a gun at your likeness.
网上还有好多这种东西  包括
Lots of other online stuff, including a...
一个比赛
contest...
比什么
For?
比最有创意的杀你的办法
For the most creative way to kill you.
哪种方法赢了
And the winner?
我不太想说  女士
Rather not say, ma'am.
我想听  把报告给我  里克
I want to hear. Just hand me the report, Rick.
基本上是  把你剥皮
It involves, essentially, skinning you.
把你的身体切成数块
Cutting your body into dozens of pieces
然后摆成美国国旗的形状
and arranging them in the shape of the American flag.
肉做白条  血做红条
Flesh for the white stripes, blood for the red.
还有吗
What else?
很多包含C打头词的威胁  女士
Lot of threats involving the C-word, ma'am.
好多好多C打头的那个词  很不幸
Lots and lots of the C-word, unfortunately.
-是"克莱尔"吗  -单子很长
- You mean Claire? - It's a long list.
如果您真想听  那我...
If you really want me to, I'll--
我不是第一个遭遇威胁的总统
Listen, I am not the first president to face threats.
我知道弗兰西斯那时  一天里能有好多
I know with Francis, sometimes there were several a day.
情况差不多吗
Is it about the same
我们现在面临的威胁
what we're dealing with here?
这...
It's...
数量明显上升
significantly up.
上升多少
By how much?
你上任以来  每天收到的威胁
There are roughly four times as many threats
大概是之前的四倍
on any given day since you took office.
而弗兰西斯死后又翻了一番
Now it's twice that since Francis died.
我以为大家都喜欢寡妇呢
I thought everyone loves a widow.
如果她还是三军统帅可能就不喜欢了吧
Not if she's also Commander-in-Chief, I guess.
这些人并不理智  总统女士
These are not rational people, Madam President.
但女士  就今天的威胁而言
But, ma'am, as far as today's threat,
关于你的第一次公开露面
regarding your first scheduled appearance--
我们要取消
We're canceling the appearance.
我们不能取消
We're not canceling.
那是军事基地
It's a military base.
那对于总统该是世界上最安全的地方了
That's got to be the safest place on Earth for a president.
一个身份未知的士兵做出了严重威胁...
An anonymous soldier has made a serious threat--
"要代表全美国
"To shoot me in the cunt
给我的屄来一枪"
on behalf of the United States of America."
是的  马克  我听说了
Yes, Mark, I heard.
这个威胁并未证实
The threat's unconfirmed.
他说他是今天出征的士兵之一
He says he's among those shipping out today.
谁都能这么说
Anyone can claim that.
还说你无权向叙利亚宣战
And that you have no right waging war in Syria.
尤其是你
You, in particular.
我们还是别去了  里克  你说是吧
I think we stay away. Rick, don't you agree?
并无证据表明这威胁可信  是吧  里克
There's no proof the threat is credible. Isn't that right, Rick?
我们的情报部门正在调查
Our intelligence division is investigating,
先遣队已经去了
and the advance team is already there,
但至少要一天
but it'll take at least a day
才能把基地查一遍
to comb through that base.
我认为副总统的提议是最佳选择
I think what the vice president says is the best course.
或许到明天  你就能...
Maybe by tomorrow you could--
明天就不是独立日了
Tomorrow is the fifth of July.
-是  女士  -那你说我怎么办
- Yes, ma'am. - So what do you suggest I do?
祝大家迟到的国庆节快乐吗
Wish the nation a happy belated birthday?
我们只是担心你的安全...
Our only concern is your safety--
不能取消
We're not cancelling.
我要让那些士兵上战场
I am sending those soldiers onto a battlefield.
美国史上第一位女性总统
The first female president of the United States
才不要在7月4日这天被人吓得说不出话
is not gonna keep her mouth shut on the Fourth of fucking July.
翻译   草草
时间轴   Ans
后期   饿得慌
校对  草草
顾问  老杜
总监  草草
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
纸牌屋
第六季  第一集
盖拉格中将也能理解的
Lieutenant General Gallagher would understand.
我可以替你出席
I could appear instead.
-替你讲话  -停下
- Speak for you. - Stop.
你担心的是我的安全
Is it my safety that concerns you,
还是我可能背书盖拉格
or my potential endorsement of Gallagher?
当然是你的安全第一
Your safety first, of course.
但单提她  这是挑衅
But singling her out, that's a provocation.
那又如何
And so?
我就不能刺激下他们吗
I can't provoke them?
你在支持一个谢泼德家族反对的
You're forwarding a candidate the Shepherds are against,
家乡州候选人
in their home state.
-经过了数月的协商  -这不是协商
- After months of negotiation. - This is not a negotiation,
这是最后通牒  签署法案  否则
this is an ultimatum. Sign the bill or what?
否则什么  马克
Or what, Mark?
弗兰西斯想给他的基金会拉资助时
When Francis was looking to finance his foundation,
你为什么给他介绍了比尔和安奈特
why did you point him towards Bill and Annette?
我没有  是雷蒙德·塔斯克安排的
I didn't. Raymond Tusk arranged it.
也或者是他们联系了他
Or maybe they reached out to him?
我不记得了
I don't remember.
有什么关系呢  他们现在跟你合作了
I-- What does it matter? They're working with you now.
我要直接见谢泼德兄妹
I need to meet with the Shepherds directly.
总统女士
Madam President.
我去基地前先见他们一面
I'll see them before my appearance at the base.
-不行  -什么
- You can't. - I what?
我会通知他们的
I'll let them know.
谢谢
Thank you.
您4:45要到基地
You're due at the base by 4:45,
然后8:30回来这里
which will have you back here by 8:30.
烟火秀9点过后开始
The fireworks show begins right after nine.
《纽约观察家》想请您过下这些照片
And the Examiner would love your okay on the photos.
那个声音的来源查出什么进展了吗
Is there any progress on the source of the sound?
总务管理局还在调查
The GSA is still looking into it.
他们在检查楼上楼下的地板
They're checking the floorboards above and below,
-以防...  -我不想再等了
- in case there's-- - I don't want to wait anymore.
请转告行政管家
Please tell the executive housekeeper
把前总统的东西收拾好
I'd like the former president's belongings packed up.
我会去处理的
I'll have it taken care of.
他多年前对你们说的那句话是不对的
It's not true what he told you all those years ago.
痛苦有两种  一种让你变强  一种毫无价值
That there are two kinds, useful and useless.
其实只有一种
There's only one kind.
痛苦就是痛苦
Pain is pain.
弗兰西斯
Francis...
我和你结束了
I'm done with you.
瞧
There.
没有痛苦了
No more pain.
你一整天都做这个吗
You do this all day?
我在接受精神科观察  赛斯
I'm under psychiatric observation, Seth.
就得这样
This is what you do.
你的新裁缝是谁
Who's your new tailor?
总得打扮得像样
You gotta look the part.
他们什么时候做出决定
So, when do they decide
你疯没疯
whether you're crazy or not?
因为如果你没疯
Because if you're not,
你应该来为我们工作
you should come work for us.
我们
Us?
你不也就才在那儿工作了五分钟吗
Have you been working there for about five minutes?
其实都一个月了
It's been a month, actually.
他还尸骨未寒呢
So his body wasn't even cold.
他也会希望如此的
It's what he would have wanted.
安德伍德基金会基本上将会参照
The Underwood Foundation was basically gonna be modeled after
谢泼德自由基金会来建设
the Shepherd Freedom Foundation.
我不需要这份工作
I don't need the job.
作为认罪杀人犯  你还挺自信啊
Well, for a confessed murderer, you're pretty confident.
我就要被赦免了
I'm about to be pardoned.
什么
Pardon?
你真觉得她会赦免你
You really think that she's gonna give you one?
你还是那样  什么都不知道
As usual, you don't know what the fuck you're talking about.
他在加夫尼下葬时  出席的人数
You know, there wasn't the kind of crowd that you'd expect for him
没有按说该有的那么多
down there in Gaffney.
他本想葬在阿灵顿公墓的
He wanted to be buried in Arlington.
而不是挨着他父亲
Not next to his father.
他妻子可不是这么说的
That's not what his wife said.
告诉我
Tell me something.
她哭过吗
She even shed a tear?
知道吗
You know...
老实说  我都有点嫉妒
I'm almost envious, to tell you the truth.
就算他进了坟墓
That even beyond the grave,
你也愿意为弗兰西斯·安德伍德赴汤蹈火
you'd do anything for Francis Underwood.
道格  你给我拿打火机了吗
Doug, do you have my lighter?
多谢
Much obliged.
那是我想的那个人吗
Was that who I thought it was?
弗莱德·安博格  他也疯了
Fred Amburg? He went off the deep end?
每个人都有点问题  赛斯
Everyone has problems, Seth.
尤其是自以为没有的那些
Especially the ones who think they don't.
-克莱尔  -安奈特
- Claire. - Annette.
你收到我的信了吗
Oh, did you get my note?
我还没能鼓起勇气读悼念信呢
Oh, I haven't had the courage to read the condolences yet.
很高兴看到你终于出来活动了
It's good to see you finally out and about.
你受了多少苦啊
Oh, what you've been through.
你最了解了
You know all about it.
很长一段时间里  我假装他还活着
Well, for a long time, I pretended he was still alive.
只是出城了
Out of town.
是我们的儿子邓肯挽救了我
It was our son Duncan that really saved me.
当然了  我们结婚可远没有
Of course, we weren't married anywhere near
你和弗兰克那么久
as long as you and Frank.
克莱尔·黑尔
Claire Hale.
九年前
Nine years.
晚春
Late spring,
太阳谷
Sun Valley.
你一点没变
You look exactly the same.
城市催人老
Well, it's cities that age you,
我总跟人那么说
it's what I tell everyone.
希望你不介意
I hope you don't mind
跟几位我们最好的朋友打招呼
saying hello to a few of our closest friends.
他们就是来喝杯鸡尾酒
They're just here for a cocktail before the--
等着太阳落山后  其余的客人到来
the sun goes down and the rest of the party shows up.
我妹妹的烟火秀算是成了个传统了
My sister's fireworks show have become a bit of a tradition.
别担心  他们会保密的
Don't worry. They know how to be discreet.
斯考特刚收购了奈克西斯安保
Scotty here just got his hands on Nexis Security.
听说你还要就此事跟副总统谈
I heard you are speaking to the vice president about this.
就是一家维和公司
It's a company of peacekeepers, mostly.
有构建国际合作的大潜力
Oh, tremendous potential to create global partnerships.
是你丈夫帮我谈妥了协议
Your husband helped me secure the deal.
我本想拉他进董事会的
I wanted to bring him onto the Board.
比尔还说...
Bill was saying...
是啊  我还说呢
Yes, I was just saying.
他们为什么要在
Why in the world do they play
烟火秀上演奏《1812序曲》
the "1812 Overture" at a fireworks show?
由柴科夫斯基创作
纪念1812年俄国人民击退拿破仑大军的入侵
作品以曲中的炮火声闻名  一些演出中还会真用大炮
那可是彻头彻尾的俄国曲子
It's Russian, for Chrissakes, in every sense.
这是塔比莎
This is Tabitha.
彼得斯  我知道
Peters, I know.
弗兰克
Frank...
-他今天本来也会到的吧  -是啊
- Wasn't he planning to be here today? - He was.
你肯定很想他
You must miss him terribly.
我曾多次跟他进行过长时间的激烈对话
I had some long and hard-fought conversations with him.
他本想帮我解决内华达州那边
He was going to help me resolve this AFL-CIO thing
旷日持久的劳联-产联的问题
that's been going on forever out in Nevada,
当然了  是在你的帮助下
with your help, of course.
工会如果阻挡创新
When the union stands in the way of innovation,
就是自寻死路
it's sentencing itself to death.
我很欣赏你坚持与党派站在一起
I do admire the way you hang on to your party.
如此忠诚
Your loyalty.
这是真的吗  据说南茜·盖拉格中将
Did I hear that Lieutenant General Nancy Gallagher
今天稍后会与你一同露面
will be appearing with you later today?
我认为她能是个好候选人
I think she'd make an excellent candidate,
如果她决定竞选的话
if she decides to run, of course.
她绝对会的
Oh, she's going to run.
总统日程很紧
The president is on a tight schedule.
失陪
Excuse me.
这真令人没想到
Well, this is a surprise.
你知道中西部的人不喜欢意料之外的事
You know how Midwesterners feel about those.
别听他的  你也该出来了
Oh, don't listen to him. It's about time you came out.
我们似乎有事要谈
Seems we have some things to discuss.
是啊
Yeah.
就这场特别选举来说  克莱尔
Well, as far as this special election is concerned, Claire,
你要知道即将退休的盖拉格女士
you need to know that the soon-to-be-retiring Miss Gallagher
是绝对不行的
is out of question.
我很高兴我们都喜欢
And I'm happy to see we're both fans
《独立宣言》
of the Declaration of Independence,
天赋人权什么的
unalienable rights and all that.
但你待会儿要发表的演讲里写着...
But it says down here in the speech you're gonna give later--
我支持盖拉格女士
Miss Gallagher has my support.
我相信马克表达了我们的担忧
I believe Mark conveyed our concerns.
希望他也表达了我的
And communicated mine, I hope.
她褪去军装就是个支持大政府的民主党
She's a tax and spend Democrat underneath that uniform.
-是简历卓越的爱国者  -克莱尔
- A patriot with a pristine resume. - Claire.
而且高调反对让私人承包商
Who is very vocal about keeping private contractors
-插手美军行动  -就算作为协商筹码
- away from US military operations. - Even as a negotiating point,
也有比她强的
you can do better than her.
我厌倦了你的拖延  总统女士
And I am tired of these delays, Madam President.
你该说到做到了
It is time for you to deliver.
-你丈夫和我有协议的  -弗兰西斯死了
- Your husband and I had an agreement. - Francis is dead.
-我们得到了承诺  -不是我给的
- Promises were made. - Not by me.
就像你一样  我也想自己谈协议
Just like you, I like to negotiate my own agreements.
别搞错了
And make no mistake about it,
中将并不是个例外
the lieutenant general is not an anomaly.
我知道  我看到了你的中期选举候选人
I know that. I've seen your list of candidates for the midterms--
是啊  大都是女人
Yes, mostly women.
我才不管他们是男是女
I don't care what sex they are.
另外  没人比我更喜欢女人了
And for the record, nobody loves women more than me.
但你的候选人名单  会拖垮这个国家
But this slate of yours, it will bankrupt the country.
会让我们倒退一代  会完全...
They will set us back a generation. They will completely--
支持我  和我的立场
Support me and what I stand for.
那是什么
And what is that?
-得了  比尔  -不  你说啊
- Oh, come on, Bill. - No, no. Tell me.
我想听听  你的使命是什么
I wanna know. What's your mission?
-我想知道你的纲领是什么  -得了
- I wanna know what your platform is. - Oh, please.
我知道你想一下肃清华府
I know you'd like to drown DC all at once.
但我这就告诉你  我不会允许的
But I'm gonna tell you right now, I cannot let that happen.
我依然相信政府
I still believe in government
相信它有能力改善其公民的日常生活
and its ability to make the everyday lives of its citizens better.
-嗯  -你不想支持我的候选人
- Yeah. - You don't wanna support my slate,
好啊
that's fine.
-克莱尔  -我只要求你别碍事
- Claire... - All I ask is stay out of the way.
你桌上有一份法案
There's a bill sitting on your desk.
这份法案耗时数年
A bill that took years...
耗费财力才获得通过
and money to get passed.
你签署了
You sign that,
我就知道我在白宫里有朋友
and I know I got a friend in the White House.
如果你不签
If not...
-那我就没有  -够了
- Then I don't. - Enough.
有她在  你是不会有好果子吃的
Nothing good happens to you when she's around.
相信我
Nothing.
你为什么赞助了弗兰西斯
Why did you come out for Francis?
他的基金会
For his foundation?
我没觉得你真喜欢过他
I don't think you ever really liked him.
可能从未尊重过他  为什么现在支持他
Probably never respected him. Why back him now?
因为他把你给了我们
Because he gave us you.
告诉我们的朋友们  我会赶上下来看烟火的
Tell our friends I'll be back down in time for the fireworks.
你要知道  我一直喜欢弗兰克
Just so you know, I always liked Frank.
喜欢他的绝望
His desperation.
很遗憾你不能留下
I'm sorry you can't stay.
我很喜欢组织我们的烟火秀
I do enjoy curating our little show.
我出行时收集了各种烟火弹
I collect a variety of fireworks shells as I travel.
意大利  西班牙  中国
Italy, Spain, China.
你知道最难做的色彩是什么吗
Do you know what the hardest color to make is?
-红色吗  -不  红色很简单
- Red? - No, red's easy.
白色也很简单
White's easy.
是蓝色
It's blue.
铜和温度的化学调剂很难弄
Very tricky chemistry involving copper and heat.
真正的亮蓝色是非常不好做的
A truly bright blue is extremely elusive.
不管弗兰西斯承诺了什么  做了什么
Whatever Francis promised or did...
都跟他一起入土了
is buried with him.
我知道
No, I know.
我们都得对他放手
We all need to let him go.
从头做起
Start from some kind of scratch.
但你肯定很难安吧
Though it must haunt you,
他就在床上你身旁长眠不起
the fact that he died next to you in bed.
亲爱的
Hon...
耐心点
be patient.
你是说  她不喜欢这名字吗
Are you saying, she doesn't like the name?
我觉得她认为名字不够完整
I think she finds it incomplete.
《综合安全法案》有什么不好
What's wrong with the Comprehensive Safety Act?
那《综合化学安全法案》呢
Comprehensive Chemical Safety Act?
也可以再回去用《精简安全法案》
Or we could go back to the Smarter Safety Act.
她会更喜欢"精简"吗
Would she like "smarter" better?
不行  得有个好缩写
No, we need a good acronym.
副总统先生
Mr. Vice President?
马克
Mark?
嗯  是啊
Yeah. Agreed.
我们还曾考虑过《不安全监管废止法案》
At one point, we talked about the Repeal Unsafe Regulation Act.
如果能再加个L开头的就是"农村"了
That's RURAL if we come up with an L.
立法吗
Legislation?
那跟其他的凑不到一起去
That doesn't make sense with the rest of it.
"农村"这词不好念  "安全"更好
"RURAL" is too hard to say. "SAFE" is good.
安全  未来
Safety. Future.
-"未来"好  -联邦综合有毒危险物...
- I like "FUTURE." - Federal Universal Toxic and Unsafe...
-去监管法案  -好
- Regulation Eradication. - Okay.
-那就《未来法案》了  -可以
- The FUTURE Act. - That could work.
可以问一下  副总统先生
May I ask, Mr. Vice President,
除了名字她还有其他疑虑吗
does her hesitation go beyond the name?
她会想通的  我猜...
She'll come around. I'm guessing...
到今天晚上吧
by the end of the day.
因为不管是什么名字
Because in one form or another,
这份法案已经在她桌上放了...
this bill has been on her desk since--
她会签的  亨利
She'll sign it, Henry.
比尔
Bill.
你要我做什么
What do you want me to do?
把她从自己的军事基地拽回来吗
Yank her from her own military base?
在人类大事件的过程中  当一个人
When, in the course of human events, it becomes necessary
有必要解除将他们与另一个人
for one people to dissolve the political bands
联系在一起的政治纽带时
which have connected them with another,
你得当机立断
you just have to do it.
切断关系
Sever the relationship.
我们国家的立国文献
Our nation's founding document,
《独立宣言》
the Declaration of Independence--
美国的独立
America's independence--
是经过艰苦斗争赢来的
was hard-fought and hard-won.
你还在听吗
Are you still there?
我们的国父构想了一个自由国度
Our Founding Fathers imagined a nation that was free.
摆脱专制
Free from despotism.
摆脱暴政
Free from absolute tyranny.
摆脱国王压迫
Free from an oppressive king.
你想弗兰西斯了吗
Do you miss Francis?
暴君有多种多样
Tyrants come in many forms.
从美国政治寡头
From the American oligarchs
企图改变社会根本
trying to change the very fabric of our society,
到在海外叫嚣的独裁者
to autocrats threatening from abroad.
我们每个人都要维护我们的命运
Now, each one of us has to defend our destiny.
在我看来
And as I see it,
抵抗暴政是战争的唯一合理理由
the fight against tyranny is the only justification for war.
我作为总统的头一百天很艰难
My first 100 days as president have been difficult.
我失去了丈夫
I lost my husband.
我们本来正要庆祝结婚30周年
We were about to celebrate 30 years together.
但我了解他的心愿
But I know what he would want.
他会希望我停止哀伤  继续生活
For me to stop mourning and carry on.
在南茜·盖拉格中将这样的女性的帮助下
With the help of women like Lieutenant General Nancy Gallagher,
我的任期将充满实干
my presidency will not rest.
南茜深深激励了我
Nancy has been an inspiration to me.
她是不倦的勇士
A tireless warrior.
我向她也向你们保证
I promise her and all of you
我会为我们的民主国家
that I will work on behalf of the rights
这241年间所赢得的权利和自由而奋斗
and freedoms earned over the last 241 years of our democracy.
当我看着今天
As I look into the eyes
站在我面前的这些勇敢战士们的眼睛
of you brave soldiers standing before me today...
是这样的
Here's the thing.
我此刻无比骄傲
I'm feeling so proud right now.
为做你们的三军统帅骄傲
Proud to be your Commander-in-Chief.
不管弗兰西斯这五年来对你们说了什么
Whatever Francis told you the last five years,
一个字都别信
don't believe a word of it.
我们国家已经241岁了  朋友们
Our country is 241 years old, my friends.
我们祝这个伟大国家生日快乐吧
Let's wish this great nation a happy birthday.
跟我一起说
Say it with me.
生日快乐  美国
Happy birthday, America!
Happy Birthday, America!
我们的情况会有所不同
It's going to be different for you and me.
再来一次
One more time.
我要对你说实话
I'm going to tell you the truth.
生日快乐  美国
Happy Birthday, America.
-谢谢你的服役  -谢谢
- Thank you for your service. - Thank you.
谢谢你的服役
Thank you for your service.
-谢谢你的服役  -谢谢
- Thank you for your service. - Thank you.
我希望你们知道我有多高兴能来见见
I want you to know how wonderful it is to be here and meet
你们这些新兵
all of you new recruits.
谢谢你
So, thank you.
谢谢你的服役
Thank you for your service.
-谢谢  -谢谢  女士
- Thank you. - Thank you, ma'am.
谢谢你的服役  你是哪来的  二等兵
Thank you for your service. Where are you from, private?
卡拉马祖  总统先生
Kalamazoo, Mr. President.
-抱歉  总统女士  -没事的
- Excuse me, Madam President. - That's quite all right.
我其实讨厌"女士"这个词
I actually hate "Madam."
让我觉得自己是管理妓院的老鸨
Makes me sound like I'm running a brothel
不是在管理国家
and not a country.
-谢谢你的服役  -谢谢  总统女士
- Thank you for your service. - Thank you, Madam President.
谢谢你的服役
Thank you for your service.
你是哪来的  伯顿二等兵
And where are you from, Pvt. Burton?
南本德  女士
South Bend, ma'am.
我爱印第安纳州
Oh, I love Indiana.
我是在您上任前不久入伍的
I enlisted right before you took office.
我向你和美国所有女性保证
Well, I promise you and every woman in this country
在我任期内
that during my presidency
会确保《平权修正案》的关键部分
the key components of the Equal Rights Amendment
终能获得通过
will finally pass.
我会确保这一点的
I'm going to make sure of it.
我希望你知道我支持你
I want you to know I support you.
你制定好计划了吗
Do you even have a plan?
你说什么
What did you say?
一个不会把我们都害死的计划
One that won't get us all killed?
天呐
Oh, man...
如果我是个男人你还会这么问我吗
Would you have asked me that if I were a man?
总统女士
Madam President!
请回答一个问题
One question, please!
一个总统安葬另一个总统
试印
我们还有多久能上飞机
How much longer till we get to the plane?
还有25分钟左右  总统女士
Just another 25 minutes or so, Madam President.
好  谢谢
Okay, thank you.
该死
Shit!
-她中枪了吗  -趴下  趴下
- Is she shot? - Stay down, stay down!
有人开枪  有人开枪
Shots fired! Shots fired!
你没事吧  总统女士
Are you okay, Madam President?
-你没事吧  -没事
- Are you all right? - Yes.
孤星安全
Lone Star is safe.
先生  刚有人企图行刺总统
Sir, someone just tried to kill the president.
我刚收到警报  她没事吧
I just got the alert. Is she all right?
这边请
This way.
林肯
Lincoln,
加菲尔德  麦金利
Garfield, McKinley,
肯尼迪
Kennedy.
刺杀成功  一共四起
Successful assassinations, total of four.
企图刺杀  是九起吗
The attempts-- Nine?
杰克逊  两个罗斯福
Jackson, both Roosevelts.
特鲁门  福特两次
Truman. Ford twice.
里根
Reagan...
第一任安德伍德  还有...
the first Underwood and...
我得说  那个企图杀我的人
I will say, whoever tried to kill me,
事与愿违了
perversely,
这是100天以来  我第一次真正感到受尊重
it's the first sign of real respect I've gotten in 100 days.
有人企图杀她
Somebody tried to kill her.
比尔
Bill.
也难怪吧
Can you blame them?
安德伍德夫妇都挺耳背的
The Underwoods have always been hard of hearing.
她不是他
She's not him.
是啊
No, no.
她的确不是
She is not.
这你最清楚了
You know that better than anyone.
公开了吗
Is it public?
被特勤局保密了  据说是标准程序
Secret Service shut it down. Standard procedure, apparently.
威胁会招致威胁
Threats beget threats.
比尔
Bill...
是你搞的吗
were you behind this?
我们要错过烟火了
We're gonna miss the show.
-你们好吗  -总统女士
- How are y'all? - Madam President.
真抱歉
Hi, I'm so sorry.
我想为延迟出发表示道歉
I want to apologize for the late departure.
我知道你们都还有家人和庆典在等着你们
I know you all have families and festivities waiting.
总统女士  我可以问问发生了什么吗
Madam President, may I ask what happened?
因为安全原因  "野兽"总统专车改道了
The Beast was re-routed due to security concerns.
很正常的
It's pretty routine.
我知道我已经挺久没来过后面了
I know it's been a while since I've been back here.
我想祝大家国庆节快乐
I just wanted to wish you all a very happy Fourth,
虽然你们要明天才能庆祝了
even if you're gonna be celebrating it on the fifth.
真抱歉
I'm so sorry.
你的讲话  之后...
Your speech, afterwards with--
是啊  那名新兵
Yes, the new recruit.
如果一名新兵  尤其还是女兵
If a new recruit, especially a female one,
不能表达自己的看法
can't speak her mind,
那我真不知我们生活在什么样的国家里了
I don't know what kind of country we actually are.
如果你们没啤酒了一定要说
And be sure to tell us if you run out of beer.
因为我敢肯定我们还有几箱
Because I am sure there's a couple of cases
是卡特政府时期留下的
left over from the Carter administration.
你是新来的
And you're new.
是的  女士  梅乐蒂·科鲁兹
Yes, ma'am. Melody Cruz.
我是首都电视的
I'm with Beltway Television.
希望大家对你还算热情
Well, I hope everyone is making you feel at home.
很热情
Very much so.
很荣幸终于见到了您
It's an honor to finally meet you.
我有点激动了  抱歉
I'm a bit overwhelmed, sorry.
-没事  我不咬人  -我知道
- Don't worry, I don't bite. - No, I know.
很奇怪  我本该采访您丈夫的
It's strange, I was supposed to interview your husband.
本来安排在他死后的几天
It was scheduled for a few days after he died.
本来会是一篇独家专访
It was going to be an exclusive.
我们已做了几次预采访
We'd had a number of pre-interviews.
也说定了一些问题
Questions we'd agreed on.
什么样的问题
Questions like?
比如  总统会赦免他吗
Like, was the president going to pardon him?
以及何时
And when?
你会吗  甚至是在他死后
Will you? Even now, posthumously?
我知道你跟《纽约观察家》做了专访
I know you did an exclusive with The New York Examiner,
但我猜那只会停留于表面
but I'm guessing that's only going to scratch the surface.
我相信你还有更多想说的
I bet you have more to say
-关于你的婚姻状况  -小姐
- about the state of your marriage-- - Miss...
科鲁兹小姐  是吧
Cruz, is it?
不知道有人跟你说过没有
I don't know if anyone's told you,
但总统来飞机这一区时
but when the president visits this part of the plane,
一般是默认为不做记录的
it's usually considered off the record.
但等我们落地了  你有什么问题
But you can ask my press secretary anything you like
都可以问我的新闻发言人
once we're back on the ground.
你今晚尤其地安静
You're especially quiet this evening.
或许我有点焦躁
Maybe I'm a little agitated.
我们的病人对烟火的反应都不佳
Our patients don't do too well when it comes to fireworks.
抱歉
Pardon me.
怎么了
Yes?
我不明白我们会面时  你为什么还开着它
I don't understand why you leave that on when we're meeting.
反正你也不会说点什么新东西
Well, it's not like you're saying anything different or new.
你照本宣科的执着都堪称可敬了
Your dedication to your script would be admirable
只是这太让人担心
if it weren't so concerning.
再过几周  我就要出席一场听证会
In a few weeks, I'll be appearing at a hearing
就你的心理状态作证
regarding your state of mind
至于你的供认
and when it comes to your confession,
有罪之人也会时不时改变说辞
even a guilty man changes his story now and then.
你听命于谁
Who do you answer to?
你为谁工作
I mean, who do you work for?
你
You.
至少该是这意思
That's the idea, anyway.
每个人都有老板的
Everybody works for somebody.
我曾经的老板是一个不肯认输的人
I worked for a man who refused to fail.
我尊重那点
I respected that.
也很感激
I appreciated it.
没有他我早死了
I'd be dead without him.
为什么
Why?
我原本是一个议员的助理
I was working as an aide for a congressman.
他理想化又天真
He was idealistic and naive.
一看就没有连任的命
Had one-term written all over him.
但我需要份工作  需要个去处
But I needed a job, a place to be.
我当时在勉强支撑
I was barely keeping it together.
弗兰西斯和我在一场活动上相识
Francis and I met at some function.
就是那种站着的活动
You know, the kind you stand up at.
我不知道他怎么知道的  但我车里有八瓶酒
I don't know how he knew, but I had eight bottles in my trunk.
那晚他找到我家时  我已经喝了四瓶
I got through four that night when he came to my door.
我不记得多少了
I don't remember much.
都很模糊了
Not clearly.
他带我回了他家
He took me to his home.
但克莱尔...
But Claire...
弗兰西斯帮我戒了酒
Francis got me dry.
我抖得好厉害  我以为自己会死
I shook so badly I thought I was gonna die.
等我终于戒掉了
And then when I was finally got clean,
他给了我第一份工作
he gave me my first job.
做助理吗
As an aide?
算是吧
Sort of.
他叫我去找爱荷华州的凯尔议员谈谈
He asked me to go talk to Congressman Kyle from Iowa.
谈什么
To what end?
说服他
To persuade him.
我做到了
And I did.
但克莱尔...
But Claire...
她对待他的方式
The way she treated him,
不论是生前还是死后
in life and in death...
但为他那样的人工作总要付出代价
But you pay a price, when you work for somebody like him.
欠下人情债
Somebody you owe.
我一个亲近的人死于了车祸
Somebody close to me died in a car accident.
所以我才违反了软禁协议
That's how I broke the terms of my house arrest.
我去看她的车祸现场了
I went to see the site of her wreck.
场面很难看  就在路边
It was twisted on the side of the road.
我站在那里
I just stood there.
事故吗
An accident?
他们说是的
So they said.
佐伊·巴恩斯呢
And Zoe Barnes?
我杀了她
I killed her.
为了总统
For the president.
以前他赢了就会这么敲
That's what he used to do when he won.
他给你留下了什么
What did he leave you with?
弗兰西斯给我的最后一样东西
Last thing that Francis gave me was
是他桌上的拆信刀
the letter opener from his desk.
是我选的  但是
I mean, I chose it, but...
或许该说他最后给我的一样东西  是一句道歉
But I guess really the last thing he gave me was an apology.
他死的那晚我跟他说过话
I spoke to him the night he died.
我的任期将充满实干
My presidency will not rest.
安德伍德总统独立日讲话
南茜深深激励了我
Nancy has been an inspiration to me.
她是不倦的勇士
A tireless warrior.
我向她也向你们保证
I promise her and all of you
我会为我们的民主国家
that I will work on behalf of the rights
这241年间所赢得的权利和自由而奋斗
and freedoms earned over the last 241 years of our democracy.
暴君有多种多样
Tyrants come in many forms...
可悲
Pathetic.
从美国政治寡头企图改变
From the American oligarchs trying to change the very...
你真不用休息一两个小时...
Are you sure you don't want to take an hour or two to--
马克  我在白宫呢
Mark. I'm inside the White House.
总统办公室里只有你我  除非你带枪了
There's only two of us in the Oval, so unless you're packing,
这对我真的是最安全的地方了
it's literally the safest place I can be.
我没带枪  总统女士
Well, I'm not packing, Madam President,
但没人会怪你休息一会儿  喘口气的
but no one would fault you for taking a breath for a minute.
我气喘得很匀
I'm breathing just fine.
我们能把这事保密吗
Can we keep news of this contained?
我已经采取了一切可能措施
I've taken every possible step, I think.
他是什么人
So who is he?
他们在路上进行了采证
Well, they did forensics on the route.
并与空中安保进行了沟通
Compared notes with the aerial detail.
国土安全部和联调局都已介入
Homeland Secretary and the Bureau were brought in.
他就没有离开他开枪的地方
He never left the place he took the shot from.
你能直截了当地回答我吗
Can you answer a single question directly and simply?
他一枪爆了自己的头
He shot himself in the head
用的是他自己的美军标准配发手枪
with his own US military-issued handgun.
我们确定枪手就是他
And we're sure he's the one?
是  支持民兵组织  反政府
Yeah. Pro-militia. Anti-government.
去年被开除军籍  有所有典型特征
Dishonorably discharged last year. All the typical markers.
特勤局确定是他
Secret Service is confident.
联调局也在调查了
And the Bureau's investigating.
比尔·谢泼德怎么拿到我的讲话的
How did Bill Shepherd get his hands on my speech?
什么
What?
媒体往往几小时前就能拿到
Well, the press usually gets it hours before.
想拿到一份应该不难吧
It wouldn't be that hard to access a copy, I guess.
我今天不会签那个的
I won't be signing that today.
你去那儿宣布你的独立
You went there to declare your independence,
也宣了战
and you declared war.
那是个错误
That was a mistake.
不  错误是我没雇幕僚长
No, the mistake was I didn't hire a chief of staff,
就有些事疏于管理
and things are slipping through the cracks.
这我就不能认同了
That's where I have to disagree with you.
我们得保持一个小圈子
We need to keep this circle small.
弗兰西斯提醒过我小心你
You know, Francis warned me about you.
我向你保证  我为你效力  总统女士
I assure you, I serve at your pleasure, Madam President.
你不能再在我的办公室里开不带我的会了
You need to stop meeting in my office without me.
是  女士
Yes, ma'am.
是特勤局牵头调查的
Secret Service took the lead.
但你相信这个说法吗
But do you believe the theory?
是一个不满的退役士兵冲我开了枪
That it was a disgruntled service person who took a shot at me?
警方调查部认为是
PID does.
我问你怎么想
I'm asking what you think.
这要看这是警告还是真正的刺杀企图
It depends if it was a warning or an actual attempt.
看他的准头
Given the accuracy,
枪手应该有足够的情报知道
the shooter would have been informed enough to know
.50子弹无法穿透"野兽"
that a .50 caliber round wouldn't penetrate the Beast.
我认为他就是想吓你
I think he wanted to scare you.
替人办事
On behalf of someone.
有很多人会对在任总统发出威胁
Lots of people make threats against sitting presidents.
我开始认为弗兰西斯是被谋杀的
I'm starting to believe Francis was murdered.
他死前
Before he died,
曾与一些很有势力的人结了盟
he aligned himself with some very powerful people.
我认为他们与他反目  并想杀死他
And I think they turned on him, and they wanted him dead,
我觉得他们还想杀我
and I think they want me dead, too.
你觉得这听上去疯狂吗
Do you think that sounds crazy?
不  女士
No, ma'am.
但我觉得我们该叫鲍曼特别探员来
But I think we need to bring in Special Agent Bowman--
这些人  这些大家族
Of these people, these powerful families,
他们倡议解散情报机构
they advocate dismantling intelligence agencies.
中情局  联调局  国土安全部
CIA, FBI, Homeland.
你知道吧
You know that, right?
-女士  -我们现在
- Ma'am-- - We cannot bring
不能再拉上任何其他人
anyone else in at the moment.
我指望你了
I'm relying on you
我知道我丈夫当初就能指望你
the way I know my husband could.
请你去查查看
So, please see what you can find.
你被称作过纳特吗
Is it ever Nate
还是一直叫纳森
or always Nathan?
纳森
Nathan.
就像弗兰西斯
Like Francis.
至少我总那么叫他
For me, anyway.
你跟道格·斯坦普谈过了吗
Oh, have you spoken to Doug Stamper?
没有
No.
我好担心他
I'm so worried about him.
他做了令白宫每个人都不耻的事
He did things no one in this White House should be proud of.
妈妈
Hey, Mom.
你那边有多少人
How many people do you have there?
不多
Not many.
至少没什么有趣的人
Nobody that interesting, anyway.
她的基地之行
Her visit to the base.
关于独立的讲话
Independence speech,
甚至士兵的出言不逊对她都很有利
even the naughty soldier is playing well for her.
她的魅力不减
Her charmed life persists.
告诉比尔舅舅我们该加把劲
Tell Uncle Bill we should step up.
我可以操纵舆论  削减她的魅力
I can manage the narrative. De-charm her.
他不会喜欢那样的
He won't like that.
反正这一切都不会让他高兴的
He's not going to like any of it,
有什么区别呢
so what's the difference?
-还是不好吧  -妈妈  就去说说吧
- I don't know. - Mom, just say the word.
相信我
Trust me.
我回复你之前什么都别做
Don't do a thing until I get back to you.
都看不出这里还是华府
Can't even tell you're still in DC.
这座城市里有些地方永远都会是个秘密
There are parts of this city that will always remain a secret.
顺说  我觉得我短期内
I don't think I'll be welcome back
不会再被邀请加入白宫记者团了
in the White House press pool anytime soon, FYI.
没关系
Doesn't matter.
她不肯跟我谈
She won't speak to me.
-采访不可能的  经过...  -她会答应的
- An interview? Not after-- - She will.
今晚  他第一次主动开口
Tonight, for the first time, he was forthcoming.
但还坚称他有罪
But still saying he's guilty?
是的  一如既往
Yeah, as always.
他提到格雷森先生的名字了吗
And did he mention Mr. Grayson by name?
没有  他只是更难过了
No. He was just more distressed.
他在恶化吗
So he's getting worse?
也可能是好转  他可算开口了
Or better, he's finally talking.
但要说短期内让他离开那里
But the idea of his leaving the facility anytime soon,
还是不可能的  这是为了他好
that's still out of the question. I mean, for his own good.
他要么真犯了罪
He's either guilty of the crime
-要么认罪是在发疯  -总统女士
- or psychotic for admitting to it. - Madam President,
谢泼德女士打到白宫来了
Miss Shepherd is on the White House line.
或许该给他开抗精神病药了
Well, maybe it's time to give him one of the antipsychotics.
或许吧  但我们得考虑他的瘾史
Possibly. But we'd have to consider his history of addiction.
对了  回答你的问题
By the way, in answer to your question,
是一把拆信刀
it was a letter opener,
弗兰西斯从桌上拿来送他的最后一样东西
the last thing that Francis gave him from his desk.
有情况再通知我  查尔斯
Keep me posted, Charles.
谢谢你
And thank you.
不客气
Sure.
你准备好了吗
Are you prepared?
什么
Excuse me.
你不记得了吗  安多弗
Don't you remember? Andover?
我们的预科学校玩笑
Our prep school joke?
我准备当掉测试
I'm prepared to fail the test.
你还好吗
Are you all right?
抱歉这么晚打来  我听说了今天的事
I'm sorry to call so late. I-- I heard about what happened today.
这些事总是不胫而走
These things have a tendency to leak out.
我担心你
I'm worried about you.
车队玻璃是防弹的
It's bulletproof, the motorcade glass.
他们抓到那男人了吗
Did they catch the guy?
你怎么知道是男人
How do you know it's a guy?
总是男人嘛
It's always a guy, right?
比尔希望修改我讲话的哪一部分
What was it Bill wanted adjusted in my speech?
就是关于
Something about...
自由的
freedom.
我惦记着你  克莱尔
You're in my thoughts, Claire.
谢谢
Thank you.
他还在我们身边  是吧
He's still with us, don't you think?
谁
Who?
弗兰克
Frank.
幸好他死前我们能跟他共度那么多的时光
We're so glad we got to spend so much time with him before he died.
他对我们说了些很有趣的事
He told us some fascinating things.
我一直在想他
He's been on my mind.
比尔和我几天前总算去了趟加夫尼
Bill and I finally went down to Gaffney a few days ago...
前去悼念
to pay our respects.
克莱尔
Claire!
我不该让他们那么做的
I shouldn't have let them.
对不起
I'm sorry.
出来吧
Come on out now.
你还在吗
Are you still there?
在啊
Yes.
救命
Help!
我知道
I know.
你想知道他究竟发生了什么
You want to know what really happened to him.
弗兰西斯那样的男人不会就那么死去
A man like Francis doesn't just die.
那就...
That would be...
怎么说的来着
what's the word?
"太巧了"
"Convenient."
深切缅怀
雷格·E·凯蒂[弗莱迪饰演者]
吉姆·泰恩斯[灯光师]
在内政  外交  经济  社会等各种议题上
共和党和民主党都持不同的观点和立场
但两党最核心的分歧  在于对联邦政府的定位不同
民主党的基本信念是"大政府能够办大事  办好事"
而共和党则认为应该限制政府的权力
大政府必然带来官僚主义和腐败
共和党总统里根曾说
"政府不是解决问题的答案  政府就是问题所在"
因此  共和党人反对政府增加税收  反对加大政府开支
还费尽心机地试图通过立法放松政府对企业公司的监管
谢泼德兄妹希望克莱尔签字的法案
就是一个要放松环保监管的法案
"野兽"是美国总统的专车
在现实生活中  美国总统特朗普刚刚更换了自己的座驾
今年9月联合国大会期间
特朗普乘坐新订制的"野兽"在纽约街头飞驰而过
据美国媒体报道  新款"野兽"是由通用公司研发的凯迪拉克
上世纪八十年代前  美国总统专车则一般是林肯
全车重约七千到九千公斤  车身厚20厘米  不仅防弹  还防生化武器
另据NBC报道  这款车还能发射催泪弹  烟雾弹以及向车后路面洒油
车门把手可以释放高压电
车内有全套急救设备  一个冰箱里储备了跟特朗普同血型的血液
车载通讯设备也是最先进的  极端情况下可以下达核攻击指令
出于安全考虑  总统车队出行时  会有一模一样的两辆"野兽"
根据合同  通用会制造10到12辆这样的车  总造价一千五百万美元左右
过去两年中  关于"美国选民是否有'厌女症'"的讨论一直不断
在2016年大选中  希拉里·克林顿意外败给了特朗普
一些媒体和希拉里的粉丝认为  社会观念上的落后
导致选民无法接受白宫内出现一位女当家
同欧洲一些国家相比  女性在美国政坛的影响力的确有限
目前在联邦政府和国会中  女性政治人物所占比重只有20%左右
包括3名女性最高法院法官  7名女性内阁部长  50个州中有6名女性州长
百名参议员中有23位女性  435名众议员中有84名女性
但是希拉里落败的主要原因  同她的女性身份关系不大
2016大选期间  民调始终显示她是历史上最不受欢迎的候选人之一
主要原因是她同老公比尔·克林顿在美国政坛活跃数十年  丑闻不断
大选过程中又爆出"邮件门"等丑闻  所以记忆力好的选民对她很不买账
有评论甚至认为特朗普当选的主要原因  正是大家讨厌希拉里
2016大选结束后  美国社会中的女性参政意识有了一个井喷
在刚刚结束的中期选举中  有创纪录的256名女性候选人参加普选角逐
最后有96名成功进入国会两院成为女议员
民主党夺回众议院控制权后  加州的南希·佩罗西也二度成为女议长
在2020大选中  民主党内预计会有大量女性候选人参加初选